https://www.epoka.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Welcome to Epoka Online!
Skip to Content
Welcome to Epoka Online!
Compare Products
EUR
DKK - Danish Krone USD - US Dollar
Epoka A/S - EOL IT Hardware Distributor
Toggle Nav HomeProductsBrocadeCiscoData DomainDellEMCExtremeHDSHPIBMIntelLenovoNetAppOEMUbiquitiWesternDigitalAccessoriesRail Kits - RackmountTransceiversBladeRail Kits-RackmountPower SuppliesSwitchesAccessoriesBladePower SuppliesRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountSwitchesTransceiversAccessoriesBladeFirewallsHost Bus AdaptersIP TelephonyPower SuppliesRacksRoutersSoftware - LicencingTransceiversBackplane - MidplaneCablesHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus Adapters (HBA)Memory Modules (RAM)Processors (CPU)Rail Kits - RackmountServersSupervisorWirelessBatteriesControllersHeatsinksI-O Modules (IO)Network ModulesRack AccessoriesRail Kits-RackmountService ProcessorsSwitchesAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesBladeCablesControllersFirewallsHard Drives (HDD)HeatsinksHost Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)IP TelephonyMemory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)Rack AccessoriesRacksRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountRoutersServersService ProcessorsSoftware - LicencingSupervisorSwitchesTransceiversWirelessAccessoriesDisk Array EnclosureHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)CablesDisk StorageHost Bus Adapters (HBA)Power SuppliesControllersHard Drives (HDD)I-O Modules (IO)TransceiversAccessoriesCablesControllersDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Power SuppliesTransceiversAccessoriesBladeControllersDisk StorageHeatsinksI-O Modules (IO)Power SuppliesRail Kits - RackmountSoftware - LicencingSystem-MotherboardsBackplane - MidplaneCablesData MoverExpansion ShelvesHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)Processors (CPU)Rail Kits-RackmountSwitchesTape StorageBatteriesControl StDisk Array EnclosureHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesRack AccessoriesServersSystem Boards - MotherboardsTransceiversAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesBladeCablesControl StControllersData MoverDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageExpansion ShelvesHard Drives (HDD)HeatsinksHost Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)Rack AccessoriesRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountServersSoftware - LicencingSwitchesSystem Boards - MotherboardsSystem-MotherboardsTape StorageTransceiversAccessoriesBladeControllersDisk StorageHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)Processors (CPU)Rail Kits - RackmountService ProcessorsStorage ProcessorsTransceiversBackplane - MidplaneCablesData MoverExpansion ShelvesHost Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesRack AccessoriesRail Kits-RackmountSoftware - LicencingStorage SystemsBatteriesControl StDisk Array EnclosureHard Drives (HDD)I-O Modules (IO)Power SuppliesRacksServersSPSSwitchesAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesBladeCablesControl StControllersData MoverDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageExpansion ShelvesHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)Rack AccessoriesRacksRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountServersService ProcessorsSoftware - LicencingSPSStorage ProcessorsStorage SystemsSwitchesTransceiversSwitchesSwitchesAccessoriesCablesDisk Array EnclosureHeatsinksI-O Modules (IO)PeripheralsRacksServersStorage SystemsSystem-MotherboardsBatteriesControllersDisk StorageHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)Power SuppliesRail Kits - RackmountService ProcessorsSwitchesTransceiversBladeCPU kitHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesProcessors (CPU)Rail Kits-RackmountSPSSystem Boards - MotherboardsAccessoriesBatteriesBladeCablesControllersCPU kitDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageHard Drives (HDD)HeatsinksHost Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPeripheralsPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)RacksRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountServersService ProcessorsSPSStorage SystemsSwitchesSystem Boards - MotherboardsSystem-MotherboardsTransceiversAccessoriesBladeControl StData MoverHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesProcessors (CPU)Rail Kits - RackmountServersStorage SystemsSystem Boards - MotherboardsTransceiversBackplane - MidplaneCablesControllersDisk Array EnclosureHeatsinksI-O Modules (IO)PeripheralsRack AccessoriesRail Kits-RackmountSoftware - LicencingSupervisorSystem-MotherboardsWirelessBatteriesComputersCPU kitDisk StorageHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)Power SuppliesRacksRoutersStorage ProcessorsSwitchesTape StorageAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesBladeCablesComputersControl StControllersCPU kitData MoverDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageHard Drives (HDD)HeatsinksHost Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPeripheralsPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)Rack AccessoriesRacksRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountRoutersServersSoftware - LicencingStorage ProcessorsStorage SystemsSupervisorSwitchesSystem Boards - MotherboardsSystem-MotherboardsTape StorageTransceiversWirelessAccessoriesBladeControllersDisk StorageHeatsinksI-O Modules (IO)PeripheralsRack AccessoriesRoutersSoftware - LicencingSwitchesTape StorageBackplane - MidplaneCablesCPU kitExpansion ShelvesHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)Power SuppliesRail Kits - RackmountServersSPSSystem Boards - MotherboardsTransceiversBatteriesControl StDisk Array EnclosureHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesProcessors (CPU)Rail Kits-RackmountService ProcessorsStorage SystemsSystem-MotherboardsAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesBladeCablesControl StControllersCPU kitDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageExpansion ShelvesHard Drives (HDD)HeatsinksHost Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPeripheralsPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)Rack AccessoriesRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountRoutersServersService ProcessorsSoftware - LicencingSPSStorage SystemsSwitchesSystem Boards - MotherboardsSystem-MotherboardsTape StorageTransceiversAccessoriesHard Drives (HDD)I-O Modules (IO)Processors (CPU)ControllersHost Bus AdaptersNetwork ModulesRack AccessoriesCPU kitHost Bus Adapters (HBA)Power SuppliesSwitchesAccessoriesControllersCPU kitHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Network ModulesPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)Rack AccessoriesSwitchesAccessoriesBladeControllersDisk StorageHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)Power SuppliesRail Kits - RackmountSoftware - LicencingTape StorageBackplane - MidplaneCablesCPU kitHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesProcessors (CPU)Rail Kits-RackmountStorage SystemsTransceiversBatteriesComputersDisk Array EnclosureHeatsinksI-O Modules (IO)PeripheralsRacksServersSwitchesAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesBladeCablesComputersControllersCPU kitDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageHard Drives (HDD)HeatsinksHost Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPeripheralsPower SuppliesProcessors (CPU)RacksRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountServersSoftware - LicencingStorage SystemsSwitchesTape StorageTransceiversAccessoriesCablesDisk Array EnclosureHard Drives (HDD)I-O Modules (IO)Power SuppliesRail Kits-RackmountStorage ProcessorsTransceiversBackplane - MidplaneControl StDisk StorageHost Bus AdaptersMemory Modules (RAM)RacksServersStorage SystemsBatteriesControllersExpansion ShelvesHost Bus Adapters (HBA)Network ModulesRail Kits - RackmountService ProcessorsSwitchesAccessoriesBackplane - MidplaneBatteriesCablesControl StControllersDisk Array EnclosureDisk StorageExpansion ShelvesHard Drives (HDD)Host Bus AdaptersHost Bus Adapters (HBA)I-O Modules (IO)Memory Modules (RAM)Network ModulesPower SuppliesRacksRail Kits - RackmountRail Kits-RackmountServersService ProcessorsStorage ProcessorsStorage SystemsSwitchesTransceiversCablesTransceiversCablesTransceiversSwitchesWirelessSwitchesWirelessHard Drives (HDD)Hard Drives (HDD)ServicesRefurbishmentTestingConfigurationLogistics ServicesSpare Parts PackagesEpoka 24/7RefurbishmentTestingConfigurationLogistics ServicesSpare Parts PackagesEpoka 24/7Customer InformationRequest a QuoteOrdersDeliveryTrack & TraceRMATerms & ConditionsTech GuidesRequest a QuoteOrdersDeliveryTrack & TraceRMATerms & ConditionsTech GuidesAboutWhy buy refurbished?End-of-life productsJobsBusiness AcademyWhy buy refurbished?End-of-life productsJobsBusiness Academy
12.000 ITEMS IN STOCKReady for day to day deliveryQUICK DELIVERYShipping within 24 hours+45 96 730 8008.30 am - 4.30 pmWorld Wide Shipping Fast & cheap shipping by DHL/FedEx
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that
you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change
this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure
that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this
request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
Epoka A/S is an end-of-life distributor of enterprise servers, storage, and networking hardware. We buy and sell refurbished hardware, as well as all other conditions including new.
© 2018 Epoka, Inc. All rights reserved.
Head OfficeLansen 19 DK-9230 Svenstrup Tlf: +45 96 730 800 About Us
WarehouseLansen 11 DK-9230 Svenstrup Tlf: +45 96 730 800 Support
Track & Trace
RMA (Return sheet)
Terms & Conditions
Delivery
Tech guides
Follow Us
This websites use cookies. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.Accept More information Loading...
